以民间汉化、天邈汉化、FOZH为基础制作
♪The Ink Spots-I Don't Want to Set the World on Fire♪
我无意燃烧这个世界
I don't want to set the world on fire
我只想点燃你心中那团火
I just want to start a flame in your heart
我的心中只有一个渴望
In my heart I have but one desire
那就是你
And that one is you
非你莫属
No other will do
我失去了获得世人称赞的雄心壮志
I've lost all ambition for worldly acclaim
我只想成为你的所爱
I just want to be the one you love
只要你承认你也有同样的感觉
And with your admission that you feel the same
我的梦想便能成真
I'll have reached the goal I'm dreaming of
相信我！
Believe me!
我无意燃烧这个世界……
I don't want to set the world on fire...
战争
War
战争从未改变
War never changes
自人类诞生以来
Since the dawn of humankind
自我们祖先第一次发现石头和骨头的杀伤力起
when our ancestors first discovered the killing power of rock and bone
鲜血就以各种名义染红大地
blood has been spilled in the name of everything
从上帝到正义，再到单纯的暴怒
from God to justice to simple, psychotic rage
2077年
In the year 2077
经过了数千年的武力冲突
after millennia of armed conflict
人类毁灭性的天性终于无法遏制
the destructive nature of man could sustain itself no longer
世界陷入了核火焰与核辐射的深渊
The world was plunged into an abyss of nuclear fire and radiation
但这却不是预言中的世界末日
But it was not, as some had predicted, the end of the world
恰恰相反
Instead
世界末日只是人类历史上另一个血腥篇章的序幕而已
the apocalypse was simply the prologue to another bloody chapter of human history
人类成功地毁灭了世界
For man had succeeded in destroying the world
然而战争
but war
战争从未改变
war never changes
在早期
In the early days
数以千计的人逃过了这次浩劫
thousands were spared the horrors of the holocaust
通过躲进巨大的地下掩体，即所谓的 “避难所”
by taking refuge in enormous underground shelters, known as vaults
但当他们出来时
But when they emerged
迎接他们的只有废墟的地狱
they had only the hell of the wastes to greet them
除了101号避难所的人
all except those in Vault 101
在浩劫当天，当火焰从天而降时
For on that fateful day, when fire rained from the sky
101号避难所的巨大钢门缓缓关闭……
the giant steel door of Vault 101 slid closed...
再也没有打开
and never reopened
你在这里出生
It was here you were born
你将在这里死去
It is here you will die
因为，在101号避难所
Because, in Vault 101
从未有人进来
no one ever enters
也从未有人离开
and no one ever leaves